Hello, my friends, and welcome to exercise number 34.
We are asked to write the program to find the duplicates in an array.
Think about an array, an array containing numbers like one four four six seven eight.
We have four and four double tickets, so we need to detect the elements that are OK.
Both the video and think about that.
Please write your solution in the comments below in order to discuss and discuss with you how you can
improve your thinking and your way of problem solving.
OK, so let's begin.
First, I will create this A..
And this is A..
And my array equal to.
One, four, four, five, six seven.
Andy, we have double objects, therefore, and.
OK.
Know how to do the algorithm to detect that duplicates.
We need to make the comparison.
And the way of the comparison is about making two nested loops that starts with one element here and
start comparing it with the others.
OK.
In order to do that.
So I need to make a loop that starts with the first element and compare to this element with all the
other elements, OK?
So it starts detecting if one equal to four for now.
So one is not duplicate, it moves that the other element.
So when it moves, I need to make a another loop.
So the big loop or the outer loop will go through all the elements and start comparing them as a starting
point.
The nested loop took the element and start comparing it, so this is four equal to four.
So this is the doubling.
Two, three, four five.
OK, so this moving inside there and inside the elements is contained in a nested loop.
OK, so it also go to the other element.
So this this moving to other element would make an outer loop and comparing this element with other
loops will make a nested loop inside it.
Let's start.
So to make this happens to loops inside that this so-called nested new, we start by entirely equal
to zero that loops it through ripping through the elements of the array and make them as a base to start
comparing length minus one and i plus plus.
OK.
This is my array that length minus one.
This is sort of I have this syntax error.
This is this look that that is indexed and iterated through it.
Its function is to move from this element to this element that this element, this element OK without
comparing anything and take them this element as base elements to start comparing now for another loop
and j equal to I class one, we started from I +1.
We are compared if we are comparing like five.
This is the base we need to compare it with the others.
So it starts from I +1.
This is the index the following number, which is I plus one.
OK J.
Less than my array dot length.
And J +, + +.
OK.
So.
Here we make that comparison.
If my array at index, I equals my array, Appendix J, then the end and we make a comparison and I
this is the I and I this is I does not equal to J.
I was not comparing that.
And so if we took four and j equal to four the same index, it's logically and absolutely would be equal.
So this is the condition where the index is not equal to the index.
We are not comparing five by itself, five at this index, we are comparing five with the other elements.
OK, so this condition is very important in order to prevent any miscommunications and any mis understanding
of the concept system that out that print and the duplicate element.
Duplicate element is my array at Index J.
OK.
So this is the algorithm that we are working with it, let's run and see.
And here we go, we have the double ticket element is equal to four.
OK.
It's very simple.
So, guys, you understand the concept we we took, we start looping through the elements and we start
this element, we compare it with other elements through this nested loop.
OK?
And we took a very, very quick example and very, very quick condition by comparing if I index my equal
index, j then put this as a duplicate element.